You were telling me that a spooner must be
able to handle many things and do them
all well.   It
's not just about doing them all well, it's about choosing
what to do well.  In my opinion, vending is a
great place to develop it,
because you are forced to do many things
at the same time.  In my case, to
tell you the truth, in the last few months I've
neglected almost everything that
wasn't the IPO, but luckily there's a
huge team that has continued to work.  In the
meantime, we've closed some deals that needed to be
integrated, so it's a compromise
between following everything and doing things
well.  There's a level of demand for
very high attention to detail, and
when we give up on detail, it's because
we know we can give up, and I don't know
how to put it, it's like I have
control over what you're saying,
"Okay, I'm okay if it doesn't come out
perfect."  What?